castingcall.club 2018-12-23

# Casting Call Club : Terms of Service

#### Privacy Policy

 **PRIVACY POLICY IN PLAIN ENGLISH**  
 _Okay, here's the deal. This site uses cookies. Here's why:_

  1. We keep track of your session, which lets you login and have an account. We also use it to make your experience better by highlighting projects you've already seen, etc.
  2. We let third-parties set cookies for analytics. Analytics helps CCC because when we build a new feature and suddenly half of the users over the age of 25 stop using the site, that means the feature was probably not a good idea.
  3. We let third-parties set cookies for ads. We're not proud of it, but we need ad money to keep the site going. If you hate ads, use ad blocker. No shame in that.

 _Right, so your personal information. What does this site do with it?_

  1. This site collects your email address. We will never ever ever ever ever ever send your email address to a third-party. It stays in our database. We only use it to email you directly about things you do on this site like when someone messages you, or when new projects are available in your search criteria.
  2. You can fill in your profile. Anything you put on your public profile is public.
  3. You can audition/apply for projects. If the project is public, so is your audition.

 _I bought something from CCC. Where did my credit/card or paypal info go to?_

  1. We use Braintree to process our credit card payments. Braintree is owned by Paypal. None of this information is ever used for anything other than making a transaction.

 _Can I delete my data?_

  1. Yes. There is a delete account button in the command center.

 **PRIVACY POLICY IN LEGAL JARGON**  
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

 **Do we use 'cookies'?**  
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For example cookies can be used to help remember and process the items in a shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

 **We use cookies to:**  
\      **•** Keep track of advertisements.  
\      **•** Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since each browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

 **If users disable cookies in their browser:**  
If you turn cookies off, Some of the features that make your site experience more efficient may not function properly.

 **Third-party disclosure**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third-party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Google**  
Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users.[ https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en](https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en)

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

 **Opting out:**  
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.
